{
    "id": "ca34ce1e21624aa0bb72c3e69740c6ae",
    "title": "Reported Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He asked her what she ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "wanted",
                "had wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4af30dabe8a44e5a7da88adbc94782d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me how my father .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "90d30f339eae4e0385b0e225a46a5c52"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me ................................ I was going home with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75c2458d81dc473198d25d253fbda4e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked us why we .................................... all sitting there doing nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54c35b65f19f45cea188092efe288f32"
        },
        {
            "question": "The prince asked the young girl ....................................... she really came from China.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cdb88fb1b6034eb785aca617ad2fafbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him if /whether he .................................... the way home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't know",
                "didn't know",
                "hadn't known"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b4a5d426ca44eb98e498df120938b2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy asked his Dad what the proper way to answer that question .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26dd297eba1241d2b24ddb57e979971a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy asked his master what he ...................................... to deserve so severe a blow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "has done",
                "had done"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fd80df09d8dd40029937c49dd3c53d6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked me who .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was I",
                "I was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89b0eaa91479450796403015ae96c20c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The traveler asked the boy if he ............................. get him a glass of water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "307956fed8224c99b489c9dd82e49329"
        }
    ]
}